Render CLI v2.9.0

Welcome! Use the Render CLI to manage your services, datastores, and
environments directly from the command line. Trigger deploys, view logs,
start psql/SSH sessions, and more.

The CLI's default interactive mode provides intuitive, menu-based navigation.

To use in non-interactive mode (such as in a script), you can set each command's --output
option to either json or yaml for structured responses. We'll also detect if stdout
is not a TTY and automatically switch to json output.

Usage:
  render [command]

Core
  deploys      Manage service deploys
  jobs         Manage one-off jobs
  logs         View logs for services and datastores
  restart      Restart a service
  services     Manage services and datastores
  workspaces   List workspaces

Auth
  login        Login to Render using the dashboard
  whoami       Display information about the current user
  workspace    Manage the CLI's active workspace

Session
  kv-cli       Open a redis-cli or valkey-cli session to a Key Value instance
  pgcli        Open a pgcli session to a PostgreSQL database
  psql         Open a psql session to a PostgreSQL database
  ssh          SSH into a service instance

Management
  blueprints   Manage blueprints
  environments List environments
  projects     List projects

Additional Commands:
  docs         Open the Render docs in your browser
  ea           Early access commands
  help         Help about any command

Flags:
      --confirm         set to skip confirmation prompts
  -h, --help            help for render
  -o, --output string   interactive, json, yaml, or text (auto: json in non-TTY contexts) (default "interactive")
  -v, --version         version for render

Use "render [command] --help" for more information about a command.
